{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702073594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702073593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702080527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702080527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702086288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702086287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702099245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702099245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702102608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702102607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702104193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702104193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702107821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702107821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702109433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702109433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702113004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702113004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702114560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702114560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702117867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702117867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702119446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702119446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702122936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702122936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702124305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702124305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702124522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702124522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702165664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702165664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702165852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702165852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702171489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702171489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:W..W.all.rand.all.stat.show.120","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702179640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702179638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" 6734f0e1-e00f-478c-8909-7b7ca7f5f2c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702190897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702190897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702191517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702191517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702192588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702192588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702193301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702193300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702194219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702194219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702195032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702195031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702195693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702195693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702196383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702196382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702197001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702197000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702200099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702200099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702200320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702200320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702201311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702201311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702202042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702202042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702202666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702202666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702209407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702209404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" ALIVICHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702211733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702211732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702214844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702214843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702216354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702216354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702216930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702216929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702217898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702217896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702218510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702218509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702226982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702226981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702227153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702227152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702228126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702228125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702230285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702230126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702233985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702233985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITIA"," userResponse":" AKITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702234831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702234831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TONGE"," userResponse":" TONGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702235043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702235043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702235616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702235615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702236890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702236889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWANI"," userResponse":" KINYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702241512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702241512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702241995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702241995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702242046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702242041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIBISHWA"," userResponse":" ULIBISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702259708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702259708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702260633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702260633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702262244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702262244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYONI"," userResponse":" MOYONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702270209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702270208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702302260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702302260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702302760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702302760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702302765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702302764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702322872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702322872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_220103"," gameId":" be9743c4-9d80-4b61-a5c6-58e570f0a41c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akafungua mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}